Once upon a time,
（アランドロン）＜あるところに
それはそれは凶悪で→
there was a barbaric, ruthless, defiant,
残忍で傍若無人で…
人を人とも思わぬ→
demon-like bastard who thought
nothing of his fellow man.
悪魔のような男がおりました＞
（男鹿）う～む…。
（ベル坊）ダブ～。
（古市）始めるぞ。
Let's begin.
男鹿の奴　何やってんだ？
What the hell is Oga doing?
何だって　かまわねぇ。
チャンスだ。
Who cares? This is our chance!
おるあぁ～！！
やあ～っ！！
うお～っ！！
Oga punch.
男鹿パンチ。
ダ！
来い　ベル坊。
タブ…。
Come here, Baby Beel.
Now, Baby Beel... Which one do you like?
さあ　ベル坊　どっちが好きだ？
ウ～ダ～　アダアダアダ！
アウ～　エイッ！
やっぱりな。
何が？
Figures.
What do you mean?
じゃあ…こっちと　こっち！
どっちが好きだ？ほい！
Then... This side? Or this side?
Which do you like?
アブ…。
（古市）それ！
ダ～！
（古市）よっ！
アブ…。
（古市）それ！
ダ～ブ～！
（古市）この赤ん坊は→
This baby only likes things
that no normal kid would like!
普通なら絶対に喜ばないものが
大好きだ。
ダ～ブ！アブ！
気に入ってるみてぇだな…
後は頼むわ。
あ　待てよ　男鹿！
Looks like he's into them.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Wait!
ダブ～ア～！
アウ？ウ？
ウグ…ウグ…。
ん？
ビエエエ～！！
ダブダブダブ！
あっ！
ダブダブダブ…！
ビエエエーッ！！
だあああ～！！
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから→
This is the story of a
juvenile delinquent who,
赤ん坊を育てることになった
不良高校生の物語…→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a child.
ただし　その赤ん坊は
普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
But this is no ordinary baby...
It is a baby Demon Lord!
魔王の子だったのです…＞
Say Hi to the BoB Brawler!
（不良達の話し声）
My body's not gonna hold up at this rate.
このままじゃ　身がもたねぇ。
だいたい何で
学校に連れて来るんだよ。
Why are you bringing him to school anyway?
家に置いてくればいいじゃね～か。
オレん家は　もうダメだ。
Shouldn't you just leave him at home?
My place is off limits... It's
been taken over by a demon.
悪魔に乗っ取られた。
コイツからも逃げらんねぇ…。
And there's no escaping him.
はあ？オレん家の方が
もっとダメだ！
Huh?
My place is even more off limits!
一昨日から半壊してんだぞ！
The day before yesterday
you half destroyed it!
Just listen, Furuichi!
まあ聞け　古市。
ダ～ブ。
Starting today, this baby and I
will be living here in your care.
（ヒルダ）今日から　この子共々
お世話になります→
ヒルデガルダと申します。
My name is Hildegarde.
Please think of me as your new daughter.
ふつつかものですが
よろしくお願い致します。
おい！まてまて！
なんだ　その誤解を招く言い方は！
Whoa! Hold it there!
Don't you think people might
take that the wrong way?
何か問題でも？
大アリだ！
Is there some problem?
Hell yeah there's a problem!
全員もれなく
固まってるじゃね～か！
Everyone's already frozen in shock!
しかし　この国では
こうするものだと聞きました。
However, I heard that was
customary in this country...
誰情報だ　コラ！
前提から　もう間違ってんだよ！
Says who, damn it?
Your assumptions are all wrong!
（父）《この国？外国の人か？》
This country?
She's from overseas?
（母）《辰巳が女の子を
連れてくるなんて…→
Tatsumi brought a girl home with him?
And she's a blond beauty, to boot!
しかも金髪美人…》
（美咲）《乳でかっ》
Her boobs are huge!
（父）
《いや　それよりも　あの子供…》
But wait, what is the baby doing...
だから言ってんだろ！オレはまだ
親だなんて認めてね～っつうの！
I told you already!
I haven't accepted that I'm the father yet!
《親？》
Father?
Even after all that you did...
あんなことまでしておいて…。
He did what?!
《あんなこと！？》
He did it
It was amazing...
What?! Tatsumi!
なに～！？辰巳！
貴様という奴は→
A punk like you doing those kinds
of things to a beauty like her...
あんなことや　そんなことを
こんな美人に！
And you still refuse to accept
her even after you got a kid?!
しかも子供まで作っておいて
あげくのはてに→
それを認めないだと～っ！
W-Wait, that's not it...
い　いや　まて…それは違うから。
（父）何が違う～っ！
見ろ～この子を！
What's not it?
Look at that kid!
どう見ても　お前の子じゃないか！
目元なんか　そっくりだぞ！
He's yours, now matter how you look at it!
He's got your eyes!
He ain't got nothin'!
そっくりじゃね～よ！
よく見ろ！
Are you blind?
あら　そっくり。
見せて　見せて。
Yes! He's the spitting image.
Let me see here...
アハハ！本当に　ふてぶてしい…→
Oh, and such a daring little boy...
小さい頃の辰巳を思い出すわぁ。
ダ～ブ。
He makes me remember when
you were little, Tatsumi.
あんた　どこの国の人？
魔界です。
What country are you from?
I'm from Makai (Demon World).
マカオ？
へぇ～日本語上手だね。
Macao?
Wow, your Japanese is really good.
本当に申し訳ありません！
I do so apologize!
こいつには責任持って
育てさせますんで！
I will make sure he takes
responsibility and raises him!
おら！お前も頭を下げろ！
おわっ！
Hey! Show some damn respect!
今後とも　ひとつ
よろしくお願いします。
I thank you so much for joining our family...
Whoa... Dad did a sliding grovel...
や～ねぇ…スライディング土下座よ。
やり慣れてるんでしょ。
He's had lots of practice.
いえ　こちらこそ
よろしくお願いします。
No, it is I who should be thanking you.
Please, call me Hilda.
ヒルダとお呼び下さい。
ダ～ブ！
…というわけだ。
ちょ…ちょっと待て！
And that's how it was.
H-Hold it a sec.
じゃあ　なにか？
ひとつ屋根の下なの？
So you're living under the same roof?
あのゴスロリ巨乳ちゃんと？
なにそれ？
With that goth-loli busty babe?
What the heck? What kind of
romantic comedy setup is this?
なにそのラブコメ展開。
オレが半壊した家で→
Why is it only you, when it's
my house that's half destroyed?!
しょっぱい思いをしてる時に
なんで　お前だけ？
食い付くとこ　そこ？
（古市）そこが重要だろ！
That's what's eating you?
That's what's important!
こっちは命が　かかってんだぞ！
My life's on the line here!
This ain't some pleasure cruise!
そんな呑気なもんじゃね～よ！
（古市）命？
Your life?
てめえ　いい加減にしろよ！
That's enough, damn you!
完全に　うちの家族
取り込みやがって→
How dare you confuse my family like that!
You seriously plan on living
here? What the hell?
マジで居つく気か？この野郎！
仕方あるまい。
There's nothing to be done about it.
The Master chose you, after all.
貴様は坊っちゃまに
選ばれてしまったのだ。
あと　夕飯うまかったぞ。
ゲップ！
Also, dinner was delicious.
くつろぎすぎだ　てめえら！
Stop making yourselves so damn at home!
フン…それに　私が坊っちゃまを
連れて出て行ったら→
However, if I take the Master and leave,
it will be you who is in danger.
困るのは貴様の方だぞ。
あ？何で困るんだよ？
アブアブ…アイ～！
Why's that?
あ…。
ダァ～。
The Master requests that you carry him.
坊っちゃまは
おんぶを要求しておられる。
でえ～い　ひっつくな！
何てことを　貴様！
Get offa me!
Such insolence... How dare you!
ビ…エエエ…。
ビエエエエ～！！
ぎゃばどぅ～！！
貴様の傍を離れると
坊っちゃまは大泣きする。
If he is separated from you,
the Master throws a tantrum.
The shock wave from the Master's crying
contains considerable destructive power.
坊っちゃまの泣き声は
衝撃波として→
すさまじい破壊力を持つ。
A precaution. When the Master
gets 15 meters away,
ちなみに　貴様が坊っちゃまと
１５メートル離れると→
泣き声の電撃は即死レベルに
達するので注意しろ。
you should be warned that the electric
waves from his voice rise to a fatal level.
ヤバすぎるだろ～が　それ！！
That's seriously dangerous!
…というわけだ。
そんな事より　男鹿！
And that's how it was.
Anyway, Oga...
その夜　ヒルダさん
どこで寝たんだ？
Where did Hilda-san sleep last night?
Furuichi, you idiot!
古市バカ！
（古市）だって～！！
But...
ダ～！？　アウ～ア？
おいおい　マジか？
本当にガキがいるよ　ケッサク。
Whoa, you kiddin' me?
He's really got a kid with
'im. What a piece a work!
だから言ったろ
男鹿をやるなら　今だって。
ダブ。
See, what'd I tell ya? If we're
gonna get Oga, now's the time.
この距離は！！
１３…いや１４．５メートル！？
男鹿くん　ダメだな～。
This distance... 13, no wait, 14.5 meters!
Oga-kun, ya gotta be more careful.
子供はしっかりと見ていないと…。
アウーッ。
You have to watch the baby
real close or else...
ヴーッ！
動くな！
え？
Don't move!
Don't move a step farther away!
それ以上　動くなよ！
動いたら　ぶっ殺す！
You move, and I kill you!
《今　何メートルだ？ちくしょ～！》
How many meters do I got, damn it?
おい　男鹿の奴
あせってやがるぜ　こえ～けど。
Hey look... Oga's breaking into a
sweat. Still scary as heck though.
（真田兄）≪どけ　コラァ！！≫
あ？
Move it, chumps!
ウッ　あんたらは！
石矢魔の双頭竜　真田兄弟！
You guys are...
It's the Twin-Headed Dragon of
Ishiyama, the Sanada Brothers!
（真田弟）
男鹿をやるのはオレ達だぜ！
We'll be the ones to do in Oga!
誰？
バカ！あれが２年の！
うわあぁ！
Who?
Idiot! Those are the second years...
Hey, now! No running away.
（阿部）≪おいおい　抜け駆けは
いけねぇな！≫
（不良）≪キラーマシン阿部！≫
It's Abe, the Killing Machine!
（阿部）この前は　よくも
やってくれたなぁ！
Oh, you did a good number on me before.
Hey, don't go forgetting me.
（下川）おっと　オレを
忘れてもらっちゃ困るぜ。
（不良）
≪グッドナイト下川まで！≫
Even Good Night Shimokawa!
なんてこったぁ！２年幹部が
せ～ぞろいじゃねぇか！
What the... All the leaders
of the second year are here!
男鹿　やべ～よ　これ！
めんどくせ～。
Oga, this is lookin' dicey.
What a pain...
おい　お前ら！もっと近付いて！
はい！！
Hey, you jerks! Stick closer!
Right!
行ってきます！
行ってらっしゃい！！
I'm headin' out!
Have a nice day!
こっち来い　コラ！
（下川・阿部）あん？
Get over here, you!
ビビッてんのか　コラ！
You chicken?
来いよ！
（下川・阿部）何だと　コラ～！
Come here!
Oh, yeah?
（下川・阿部）ぐわ～！
男鹿１５メートル　ギリギリパンチ！
Oga "barely 15 meters" punch!
（真田兄）へえ…。
やるね　ルーキー。
Hey? Not bad, rookie.
（真田兄）真っ二つにしてやんよ。→
I'll saw you completely in half!
With my secret technique, the Texas Chainsaw!
オレ達の必殺技
敵刺すチェーンソーでな！！
（真田兄弟）死ねやぁ～！！
Die!
Then I'll use...
じゃあ　こっちは！
メ！リ！コ！ミ！
Ground pound!
ダーブ！
パーンチ！！
Punch!
ダブル瞬殺！
ダ～ッ！！
A two-fer!
あ　いや　スンマ…。
Uh, we're sor...
ただいま！お帰りなさい！
Daddy's home!
Welcome back!
わ～っ！
次　勝手に離れたら踏み潰すぞ！
ダァ～！
Next time you make off alone
like that I'll stomp you flat!
アッ　アウ…。
あっ。
ビエエエエ～！！
ダ～ブ！
ちくしょ～。
God damn it.
Oh, you're home Tatsumi?
おお　辰巳　帰ったか。
先に食べてるわよ。
We already started eating.
あなた　お帰りなさい。
Welcome home, Dear.
なに和やかに
食卓　囲んでんだよ！
Why are you all calmly sitting
around the dinner table?
一家団欒で
カレー食ってんじゃねえ！
Don't chow down on curry like
we're one happy family, damn it!
このカレー
ヒルダさんが作ったのよ。
Hilda-san made this curry!
ベルちゃんのご飯も
こっちに　ありまちゅよ～。
We've got dinner for you too, Beel-chan.
料理も上手だし　ホントに
辰巳には　もったいないわよね！
She's even good at cooking... She's
totally wasted on you, Tatsumi.
こいつは悪魔なんだぞ！
She's a de-mon!
わかってる　わかってる。
ヒルダさんは　あくまで→
Yes, that's right.  She's
the one to be your wife...
お前の嫁さんだ。アッハッハ！
どうぞ　お義父さん。
うん。おっとっと…。
Let me fill you up, Father.
ところで式は　いつだね？
By the way, when is the shiki?
"Shiki" = Ceremony
死期？教えても
よろしいのですか？
Shiki? Are you sure you want to know?
"Shiki" = Time of Death
こらこらこら～っ！ちょ…。
ダブ。
Whoa, whoa, hold it!
辰巳　そんなイライラしていないで
先にお風呂に入って。
Tatsumi, don't be so cross.
How about taking a bath first?
ベルちゃんは　私が見てるから。
安心しろ。
I'll look after Beel-chan for you.
Do not worry. It is 14 meters between
the bathroom and the living room.
風呂から食卓までの距離は
１４メートル。
そこのラインを越えなければ
問題ない。
As long as you don't go beyond
that line, you should be fine.
ギリギリじゃね～か…。
That's cutting it damn close...
…ったく。
Sheesh...
ん？
（アランドロン）チャオ。
Ciao!
何だよ　テメエ…。
What that hell are...
んん…もう　お忘れに？
You forgot me already?
次元転送悪魔の
アランドロンでございます。
I am the dimensional transference
demon, Alaindelon.
That ain't what I asked!
そんなこと聞いてんじゃねぇ！！
何しに来た？
What are you doing in here?
ヒルダ様に頼まれまして
坊っちゃまとの距離のご報告に…。
I was asked by Hilda-sama...
To report the current distance
between you and the Master.
１２．７メートル…１２．９メートル…。
12.7 meters...12.9 meters...
おおおおっと～１４．３メートル。
Ooh... 14.3 meters...
１３．９メートル…１３．３メートル…。
13.9 meters... 13.3 meters...
おおおおっと～１２．５メートル。
Oh, oh...! 14.5 meters!
落ち着いて入ってられるか～！！
How am I supposed to relax
in the bath like this?
Finally asleep...
やっと寝たか。
そのようですね。
That is how it seems.
まだいたのか！
You're still here?
（アランドロン）ンーッ！
ぶはっ！
は～っ　は～っ　はっ…。
What are you doing here?
何しに来たの　お前…。
He was loitering around in front
of the house, so I transfered him.
こちらの家の前を
ウロウロとなさっていたので→
転送してさしあげました。
お前の事が気になってさ。
I was worried about you, see...
ヒルダさんと　ひとつ屋根の下で
いろいろ大丈夫かって。
Are you really okay living under
the same roof as Hilda-san?
静かにしろ！
坊っちゃまが目を覚ます。
Be quiet! You will wake the Master.
フ～。
こうして見てると　とても
魔王の子には見えないなぁ。
When you look at him like this, he really
doesn't look like a baby Demon Lord.
安心しろ。やがて成長すれば→
No need to worry. As he grows up, he
will gain the power to destroy humanity.
人類を滅ぼす力を持つようになる。
安心できね～よ。
Oh, I'm worried all right.
Wait, so does that mean like... the future
of humanity rests on your shoulders?
なあ　もしかして人類の未来ってお前の肩にかかってる？
フ…なんてね。
Haha?
ハッハッハ…。
アハハハ…。
ハハハ…。
ムハハハ…。
うるせえ～っ！
アウ　アイ？
Shut up!
つ～か　そもそも
なんでオレが親なんだよ！
And hey, why does it have to be me?
他にいくらでもいるだろ。
そういうわけにはまいりません。
There's got to be plenty
of other people out there.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
先日もお話した通り　坊っちゃまは
なんせ魔王ですからね。
As we discussed the other day, the
Master is a Demon Lord, you see...
He only cares for those with great strength.
まず　強い者にしか惹かれません。
いや　まぁね。
あ　ゆるんだ。
Well, I suppose I fit that...
Oh, that he likes.
そしてさらに
凶暴で残忍で傍若無人で→
And in addition to that, barbaric,
ruthless, and defiant bastards
who think nothing of their
fellow man are perfect.
人を人とも思わないヤローなら
最高です。
強ければ強いほど　凶暴であれば
あるほど坊っちゃまは懐くのです。
The stronger and more ruthless the person
is, the more the Master takes a liking to them.
待て！ということはあれか？
オレより凶暴な奴がいたら→
Wait! Then that means...
If I can find a person more brutal than me,
then Baby Beel will get attached to him!
ベル坊はそいつに懐き
オレは解放されるってことか？
I'll be free!
（男鹿・アランドロン・古市）アハハハ…。
バカか貴様ら！
Such idiots!
（男鹿・アランドロン・古市）アハハハ…。
（大魔王）ワハハハ…。
（ピカッ　ドゴーン）
（大魔王）グァハハハハ！
おろかな奴らめ。→
My pitiful ones!
この手で
メチャメチャにしてやる！→
I will scramble you good!
Destruction! Total annihilation!
破壊だ　大破壊だ！ガハハハ…。
うるさいんですけど。
He's kind of annoying...
ここだけだよ　大声出してんの。
（大魔王）あ～ワリイワリイ。
Why does he only rant during our games?
Oh, my bad.
I ain't slept for a week, so
I'm kinda hopped up, ya know?
１週間　寝てないと　変な
テンションになっちゃってさ。→
I'm real sorry everybody!
みんなもゴメンゴメンゴ。
でも　いいよね！大魔王だし。
But you'll forgive me 'cause
I'm the Great Demon Lord!
（側近）大魔王様。
（大魔王）よぉ！久しぶり！→
Great Demon Lord...
Yo, wazzap.
How's the child rearin' coming?
子育ての方はどう？わしの息子は
ちゃんと人類を滅ぼしてくれそう？
My son looking like he'll destroy humanity?
Well, for the time being, this man
has become Lord Beelze's father.
まあ　とりあえず
この男がベルゼ様の親に。
（大魔王）
へえ～なかなか凶悪そうで
いい顔してんじゃん。→
He's got a pretty barbaric face there. Nice.
Ooh, ron!
あ～それ　ロン！ワラ人形
五寸釘トンカチの丑三ツ暗刻ね。→
I gots a three closed triples with
straw dolls, 5 nails, and hammers!
Oh, yes... My son's favorite toy.
あ　そうそう　わしの息子の
大好きな　このオモチャ→
I totally forgot to hand it over.
渡すの忘れてたからさぁ
宅配便で送っといてくれる？
Can you send it DeadEx?
ん～。どこだ？どこにいる！？
Where...
Where is he...
Where's a bastard that's stronger
and more brutal than me?
オレより強くて凶暴なヤローは！？
オメーかコラー！！
Is it you?!
No way, man!
ちげ～よ！
アウ～ダ～ブ！
オメーは悪いか！？
いえ　全然っす！
How 'bout you? You bad?
N-Not at all, dude!
アイ～アイ…。
あ　あれ！？
あ？アバレオーガ！
Look at that!
It's the Rampaging Ogre!
いや　その上！
（不良達）うわあああ！！
No! I mean, on top of him!
（不良達）くっさ～！！
Ewwww!
Something smells...
くさい？まさか！！
He didn't....
That ain't somethin' you do on
people's heads, god damn it!
てめえ　人の頭の上で
してんじゃね～！
ビエエエエーッ！
（不良達）お？
ヒルダさん　何しに？
Hilda-san! What brings you here?
先ほど魔界からの宅配便で→
I received an express delivery
from the Demon World,
坊っちゃまのお気に入りのオモチャが
届いたので持ってきてやった。
and have brought it immediately
to give to the Master.
男鹿辰巳はどこにいる？
Where is Oga Tatsumi?
Oga's off searching for someone strong.
男鹿なら今　強い奴を
探しに行ってるとこだけど。
フン　往生際の悪い男だ。
That man has a hard time giving up.
Hey, girly... How'd you
like to go a round with me?
（下川）そこの小猫ちゃん
オレと一戦　交えてみない？
Who the hell are you?
なんだ　お前は？
君の瞳にグッナイ！
I say, Good Night to those eyes of yours...
（シャキーン　バゴーン）
Good Night!
グッナ～イ！！
（爆発音）
What was that?
何だ　何だ！？
（不良達）うわ～！！
Too strong!
メッチャ強え～！
That one's brutal!
あっちに強い奴がいるのか？
ダ～ブ。
There's someone strong over there?
Oga Tatsumi... So that's where you were.
男鹿辰巳　そこにいたか。
なんだ　やんのかコラ！
What the hell is this all about?
Well...
いや　やっぱコイツを
連れてってくれるのか？
You've decided to take him and leave, right?
ダ～ブ！ヤイヤイ！
ちょっと待て泣くぞ！
来んな　来んな！！
Wait a second! Don't cry! Don't do it!
あ～！うわ～～！！
ダ～ブ～ビエエエ～ッ！
（ガランガラン）
ビエエエ…アウ？
ハ～！！
あ？
ダ～ブ！アイヤ　アウ～！ダ～ブ！
（ガランガラン）
ダ～ブ！
ダ～ブ　ウーアイ　ダー！
（ガランガラン）
It sure makes an awful racket.
…にしてもヒドい音だな。
What nonsense. It's a lovely
sound that pleases the Master.
何を言う。坊っちゃま好みの
心地よい音色であろう。
アイ～ヤ！
（ガランガラン）
Anyway, have you found someone
stronger and more brutal than you?
それより　貴様よりも強くて
凶暴な奴は見つかったのか？
No, not yet.
いや　まだだ。
フン　この荒れ果てた地を→
Isn't there some Great Demon Lord
that rules this god-forsaken place?
統治する大魔王様のような
お方はいないのか？
それだ！大魔王
学校でいえば校長じゃね～か！
That's it!
If you're talking about the Lord of a
school, then you mean the Principal!
なるほど！
そういう考え方もあるな。
I see! I suppose you could think that way.
I dunno what the guy's like,
どんな奴か知らねえが
全国一の不良校の校長を→
but if he's the Principal of the worst
school in the country, he's gotta be strong!
やってるってことは
相当　強いに違いねえ！
ベル坊もきっと懐くはず！
I'm sure that Baby Beel will take to him!
In here...
この中か…。
Who knows how frightful
this Principal will be?
いったいどんな恐ろしい校長が…。
いくぞ古市。
Here I go, Furuichi...
（校長）ヒィ！
ん？
（校長）ううううう…。
あんたが校長？
You're the Principal?
ある意味　こんな格好でこの学校の
校長やってるってのは最強かも。
Yeah, in a way, you gotta have balls to be
the Principal of this school wearing that...
ああ…。
ダ～ブ！
（腹の虫）
アウ！
アウ～！ビエエエエ～！
うわああああ～！
（爆発音）
（不良達）うわぁ～！！
ハアハア…今度は何なんだ？
What is it now?
（腹の虫）
ビエ～。
The Master is hungry. I believe
I prepared lunch for him.
坊っちゃまは
お腹を空かせておいでだ。
昼ご飯は持たせてあるはずだ。
どこへやった？
Where is it?
It was in the classroom you destroyed!
てめえが壊した教室だよ！
あそこに置いてあったのか。
You left it there?
Hold it!
ちょっと待った～！
ここは当然　母乳では？
This is where you nurse him with those...
グワッ！！
The Master prefers the milk from
the nine-headed King Hydra,
坊っちゃまの好物は　６６０万人の
魔界の住人の命を奪った→
who took the lives of 6.6 million
residents of the Demon World.
９つの首を持つ
キングヒュドラの乳。
Yeah, I don't got that.
そんなのね～よ！
The closest thing in the
human world would be...
人間界で近いものといえば…。
≪押すなよ！≫
どけ！
Move it.
（不良達）どわっ！
This.
これだ。
牛乳かよ！
The Milk
Cow's milk?
ダー。
I gots it!
≪わしがもろた！≫
エッヘー！
待てや　コラッ！
Hold it, you!
アイ…。
アッ！
イッ…エグッ　ビエエエエーッ！
（不良達）うわぁ～！！
（爆発音）
（カラスの鳴き声）
Listen up, Baby Beel.
いいか　ベル坊。男ってもんは
そう簡単に泣いちゃいかんのだ。
ダ！
A man can't go crying so easily.
Plus, you're a Demon Lord!
ましてや　君は魔王だろ？
ダ！
No, not "da".
ダじゃね～よ！
わかってんのか　お前？
ダ！
Do you really understand?
男って～のはなぁ
つらい時ほど泣いちゃいけねえ。
The tougher it gets, the less a
man should cry. Do you know why?
何故だかわかるか？
ダァ？
涙と一緒に流れちまうからだ。
悔しさとか悲しさってもんがよ。
Because tears wash away
the pain and suffering.
そういう思いは
いざという時　武器になる。
But those emotions become weapons
when you truly need them.
アイ？
So that's why you can't
just go off like that.
だから　簡単に
たれ流しちゃいけね～。
When you want to cry, laugh it off!
That's what being a man is, got it?
泣きたい時こそ笑って乗り越えな。
それが男ってもんだ。わかるな！
ダッ！
（真田兄弟）ギャハ！
あ？ベル坊！
Baby Beel!
We gots yer kid!
ガキは預かったぜ！
おい　コラ！
Why, you...
《１５メートル以上　離れたら即死》
If he gets more than 15
meters away, I'm dead meat!
No way! We're going 50 kilometers an hour!
ウソだろ？５０キロは出てるぞ。
非常識なヤローだぜ！ダ…。
This guy's unreal!
Don't cry!
泣くな～っ！
ウッ…。
あと３メートルでございます。
You have 3 meters!
2.9... 2.8... 2.7...
２．９…２．８…２．７。
何しに来た！私をお使いください。
What are you doing here?
Please, use me!
さあ！
うわっ！
Now!
ヘヘヘ…なに～っ！？
What the...
ハッハッハッ…。
（ブレーキ音）
（アランドロン）アー！アガッ！！
アイッ　ウー。
ううっ…。あ…。
Dude, the big guy's messed up...
おい　おっさん跳ねちまったよ。
パッカン。
Pop!
Pop?
パカッ？
え～！
おぉ！！
アウ～。
Nice one. Seems like you didn't cry.
えらいぞ
泣かなかったみてえだな。
Oga, you bastard...
男鹿てめえ！
ゆるせねえ！
We won't forgive you!
いくぜ！
ダー！
Here we go!
アウー！！
ウァアアアア！
魔王～パーンチ！
Demon Lord Punch!
ウォッ！アァー！！
ダ～ブ！
帰るか！
Let's go home.
ダ　アイー…。
（ガランガラン）
（カランカラン…）
ビエエエエーッ！
アー！！
I am so gonna stick him with someone else!
絶対　誰かに押し付けてやる！！
（爆発音）
フン　まだまだだな。
He's still got a lot to learn.
ビエエエエーッ　ダウ！
Damn it all... I'm stuck with him.
What's so bad about it? You get to live
together with Hilda! I wanna live with Hilda!
If you are really so envious
about that, I'll think about it.
Really, Hilda-san?
Next time on Beelzebub: "Are there any
strong, ruthless bastards around here?"
Are you talking about me?
Who?